Raymond Pearl Papers ca.1895-1940 Mss.B.P312
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Bell, James F., 1919-1939; 11 folders (Box 2-3)
    - Folder 6 (Box 3)
      Corby, R. L.
    - Folder 7 (Box 3)
    - Folder 8 (Box 3)
      Bell, C. Herbert
    - Folder 9 (Box 3)
    - Folder 10 (Box 3)
    - Folder 11 (Box 3)
  - Bell, W. Blan (Box 3)
  - Bellock (Box 3)
  - Bénézet, Louis P. (Box 3)
  - Berkson, Joseph, 1926-1940; 4 folders (Box 3)
    Biographical and personal data; Educational matters; Fellowships, assistantships; Graduate study; Human evolution, physical anthropology; Johns Hopkins University; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Publication; Reviews; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
    - Folder 1 (Box 3)
    - Folder 2 (Box 3)
    - Folder 3 (Box 3)
    - Folder 4 (Box 3)
      Prendergast, John J.
  - Bernard, Leon, 1928-1931; 3 folders (66 items) (Box 3)
    International Union for the Scientific Investigation of Population Problems
    - Folder 1 (Box 3)
      Viguie, A.
      Huber,
    - Folder 2 (Box 3)
    - Folder 3 (Box 3)
  - Bertalanffy, Ludwig von (Box 3)
  - Bibliography (Box 3)
  - Bingley, George A. (Box 3)
  - Biodynamica (Box 3)
  - Biological Abstracts, 1925-1938; 2 folders (71 items) (Box 3)
    Publication -- Biological Abstracts
    - Folder 1 (Box 3)
      Bioletti, Frederic T.
      Detlefsen, J. A.
      Schramm, J. R.
      Rand, Frederick V.
      Sturgeon, H. N.
    - Folder 2 (Box 3)
      Teisen, Aase
      Schramm, J.
      Flynn, John E.
  - Biological Bulletin (Box 3)
    Moore, Carl R.
    Redfield, Alfred C.
  - Birth Control Federation of America, 1931-1940; 3 folders (Box 3)
    Conferences and symposia; Political issues -- Birth control; Population, demography; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs
    - Folder 1 (Box 3)
      Sanger, Margaret
      Palache, A. H.
      Pearson, Adelaide
      Moore, Hazel
      Rose, Florence
      Hanau, Stella
    - Folder 2 (Box 3)
      Burch, Guy Irving
      Little, Clarence Cook
      Madden, Jane
      Pierson, Richard N.
      Morris, Woodbridge E.
    - Folder 3 (Box 3)
      Wood, Mabel Travis
      Rose, D. Kenneth
  - Bissonnette, T. Hume (Box 3)
  - Bittner, John J. (Box 3)
  - Blacker, C. P. (Box 3)
  - Blakeslee, A. F. (Box 3)
  - Bliss, Sidney (Box 3)
  - Bloodgood, Joseph Colt (Box 4)
    Welch, William
  - Boas, Franz (Box 4)
  - Bonnell, Robert O. (Box 4)
  - Book Reviews (Box 4)
  - Boquet, D. (Box 4)
  - Bordley, John Earle (Box 4)
  - Borges Vieire, F. (Box 4)
  - Boring, Alice M. (Box 4)
  - Boring, Edwin G. (Box 4)
  - Boston Society of Natural History (Box 4)
    Allen, Glover M.
  - Boudreau, Frank G. (Box 4)
  - Bowerman, Walter G. (Box 4)
  - Bowman, Isaiah (Box 4)
    Bentham, Franklin Mott
    Ionesco, C.
  - Boys, C. V. (Box 4)
  - Breder, C. M., Jr. (Box 4)
  - Brekhus, Peter J. (Box 4)
  - Bridges, Calvin M. (Box 4)
  - Bridgman, Frederick J. (Box 4)
  - Brink, R. A. (Box 4)
  - Brinton Associates (Box 4)
  - British Association for the Advancement of Science (Box 4)
    Bone, James
  - Britton, S. W. (Box 4)
  - Bromley, Dorothy Dunbar (Box 4)
  - Brooks, S. C. (Box 4)
  - Brothers of the Book (Box 4)
  - Brown, Edward (Box 4)
  - Brown, Lawrason (Box 4)
  - Brues, C. T. (Box 4)
  - Bruhls, C. T. (Box 4)
  - Brun, B. Lucien (Box 4)
  - Buchholz, H. E. (Box 4)
    Saturday Night Club
  - Buck, Walter H. (Box 4)
  - Buck, Mrs. Walter H. (Box 4)
  - Bulletin d'Histologie Appliquée (Box 4)
    Policard,
  - Bumpus, Dr. (Box 4)
  - Bunn, Edward B. (Box 4)
  - Burden, Henry (Box 4)
  - Bureau Der Medinischen Refgratenblätter (Box 4)
  - Burnett, Paul M. (Box 4)
  - Burr, H. S. (Box 4)
  - Burrows, J. C. (Box 4)
  - Burrows, Montrose T. (Box 4)
  - Burrows, William (Box 4)
  - Butschli, Otto (Box 4)
  - Buxton, P. A. (Box 4)
  - Cairns, Huntington (Box 4)
  - Campbell, James A., 1906-1940; 2 folders (76 items) (Box 4)
    Educational matters; Fellowships, assistantships; Publication; Teaching; Travel -- Europe
  - Cannon, Walter B. (Box 4)
  - Carey, Henry R. (Box 4)
  - Carey, James, 3rd (Box 4)
  - Carlton, Newcomb (Box 4)
  - Carnegie Institution of Washington (Box 4)
    Woodward, R. S.
    Walcott, Charles D.
  - Carr, A. F., Jr. (Box 4)
  - Carrel, Alexis (Box 4)
  - Carty, John J. (Box 4)
  - Caspari, Ernst (Box 4)
  - Castle, William E. (Box 4)
  - Cathcart, Maxwell (Box 4)
  - Catlin, G. E. G. (Box 4)
  - Cattell, J. McKeen (Box 4)
  - Cattell, R. B. (Box 4)
  - Caxton Printers, Limited (Box 4)
  - Chaddock, Robert E. (Box 4)
  - Chapman, Ross McC. (Box 4)
  - Chapman, V. J. (Box 4)
  - Charles, Enid (Box 4)
  - Charo, Walter J. (Box 4)
  - Chemisches Zentralblatt (Box 4)
    Pflückg, M.
  - Cheslock, Louis (Box 4)
  - Chesney, Alan M. (Box 4)
    Johns Hopkins University. School of Medicine.
    Reed, Lowell
    Johns Hopkins University. School of Hygiene and Public Health.
  - Chester, Kenneth Starr (Box 5)
    Carbone, D.
    Arnaudi, C.
    Pearl, Maud D.
  - Chicago Record-Herald (Box 5)
  - Chicago Writing Machine Company (Box 5)
  - Child, Dr. (Box 5)
  - Chickering, A. M. (Box 5)
  - China Journal (Box 5)
    Sowerby, Arthur DeC.
  - Chinard, Gilbert (Box 5)
  - Chittenden, F. H. (Box 5)
  - Chronica Botanica (Box 5)
    Verdoon, Fr.
    Hunik, J.
  - Chugerman, Samuel (Box 5)
  - Claoné, C. (Box 5)
  - Clark, B. Preston (Box 5)
  - Clark, George G., 1913-1929; 34 items (Box 5)
    Biographical and personal data; Dartmouth College
  - Clark, Hubert Lyman (Box 5)
  - Clark, Janet H. (Box 5)
  - Clarke, Francis (Box 5)
  - Clarke, George L. (Box 5)
  - Cleland, Ralph E. (Box 5)
    Russianoff, Penelope Pearl
  - Clendening, Logan (Box 5)
  - Clinical Club (Box 5)
    Colston, J. A. C.
    Looper, Edward A.
    Koontz, Amos R.
    Waters, Charles A.
    Johnson, Robert W.
    Tappan, Benjamin
    Edwards, Monte
    Chisolm, J. Julian
  - Cobb, W. Montague, 1937-1940; 37 items (Box 5)
    Biographical and personal data; Howard University; Human evolution, physical anthropology; Publication; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Colby, John C. (Box 5)
  - Cole (Box 5)
  - Cole, Leon Jacob, 1900-1929; 9 folders (230 items) (Box 5)
    Biological Survey of the Great Lakes; Embryology, developmental genetics; Graduate study; Human genetics; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Physiology; Protozoan genetics; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Teaching -- University of Michigan; University of Maine; University of Wisconsin; Yale University
  - Collins, James H. (Box 5)
  - Colton, Harold S. (Box 5)
  - Comitate Italiano (Box 5)
    Camavitto, Dino
  - Commission on Medical Education (Box 5)
    Rappleye, Willard C.
  - Commonwealth Fund (Box 5)
    Quin, Barbara S.
  - Compton, Karl T. (Box 5)
  - Concilium Bibliographicum (Box 5)
  - Congenital Malformations. Problem (Box 5)
  - Conklin, Edwin G. (Box 5)
    Quarterly Review of Biology
    Nellemose, W.
    Comité De L'Encyclopédie Française
  - Connolly, Helen S. (Box 5)
  - Cook, William W. (Box 5)
  - Coolidge, Calvin (Box 5)
  - Cooper, Charles G. (Box 5)
  - Cooper Union Forum (Box 5)
    Martin, Everett Dean
    David, Blanche C.
  - Cornelius, James T. (Box 6)
  - Cornell University (Box 6)
    Farrand, Livingston
    Patterson, Woodford
    Mansfield, James S.
  - Correns, C. (Box 6)
  - Cowdry, E. V. (Box 6)
  - Cox, Eugene A., 1929-1940; 2 folders (46 items) (Box 6)
    Biographical and personal data; Philosophy of science; Political issues; Publication; Russian politics and science; World War II -- Impact on science
    - Folder 1 (Box 6)
    - Folder 2 (Box 6)
      Kizer, Benjamin H.
      Howard, Pendleton
  - Craft, W. A. (Box 6)
  - Crampton, C. Ward (Box 6)
  - Crank Letters (Box 6)
  - Crawford, Stanton C. (Box 6)
  - Creaser, C. W. (Box 6)
  - Crew, F. A. E. (Francis Albert Eley), 1921-1938; 2 folders (51 items) (Box 6)
    Eugenics; International Congress of Genetics -- Seventh Congress; International Union for the Scientific Investigation of Population Problems; Political issues; Population, demography
    - Folder 1 (Box 6)
      Ross, Halford
    - Folder 2 (Box 6)
      Fischer, Eugen
      Wilson, E. B.
  - Crittenden, A. R. (Box 6)
  - Cross, Wilbur (Box 6)
  - Crowe, Robert S (Box 6)
  - Crum, X. X. (Box 6)
  - Cumings, E. R. (Box 6)
  - Cummins, Charles A. (Box 6)
  - Cushing, Harvey (Box 6)
  - Cutter, Ruth M. (Box 6)
  - Dabney, William M. (Box 6)
  - Daland, Ernest M. (Box 6)
  - Dalrymple-Champneys, Sir Weldon (Box 6)
  - Damon, S. R. (Box 6)
  - D'Amour, Fred E. (Box 6)
  - Dana, Charles L. (Box 6)
  - Dana, John Cotton (Box 6)
  - Danchakoff, Vera (Box 6)
  - Daniel, J. Frank (Box 6)
    Pearl, Maud DeWitt
  - Darlington, P. J., Jr. (Box 6)
  - Dartmouth College, 1933-1944; 3 folders (Box 6)
    Dartmouth College; Educational matters; Invitations; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Solicitations for support or contribution
    - Folder 1, 1933-1937 (Box 6)
      Heywood, Spade
      Dickerson, Albert I.
      Cloton, R. C.
      Heyward, Sidney C.
      Hoban, Owen A.
      Stone, Robert M.
    - Folder 2, 1938-1940 (Box 6)
      Hopkins, Ernest M.
      Evans, George H.
      Ballard, W. W.
      Gerould, John H.
      Hayward, Sidney C.
      Parkhurst, George H.
      Clark, George G.
      Rugg, Harold G.
      Graydon, Charles W.
      Ham, W. H.
      West, Herbert F.
      Emerson, Sumnar R.
      Winchester, Philip H.
    - Folder 3, 1941-1944 (Box 6)
  - Darwin, Leonard, 1918-1924; 13 items (Box 6)
    Behavioral genetics, IQ; Evolution; Publication; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Daubenmire, R. F. (Box 6)
  - Davenport, Charles B. (Box 6)
  - Davies, G. R. (Box 6)
  - Davis, D. J. (Box 6)
    Knobel, Gratia Esher
  - Davis, David E. (Box 6)
  - Davis, Donald W. (Box 6)
  - Davis, H. Jackson (Box 6)
  - Davis, Janover W. (Box 6)
  - Davis, Katherine Bement (Box 6)
  - Davis, Watson (Box 6)
  - Day, Arthur L. (Box 6)
  - Day, Clarence A. (Box 6)
  - Daz-Schriftleitung (Box 6)
  - Dead Letter Office (Box 6)
  - Deale, J. E. (Box 6)
  - Dean, A. S. (Box 6)
  - Deason, Hilary J. (Box 6)
  - Deetjen, Chr. (Box 6)
  - Deevey, Edward S., Jr. (Box 6)
  - DeKruif, Paul H., 1913-1940; 2 folders (102 items) (Box 6)
    Biographical and personal data; Publication; Reviews -- Flexner, Simon; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Deom, Georges (Box 6)
  - DePorte, J. V. (Joseph V.), 1925-1940; 52 items (Box 7)
    Biographical and personal data; History of biology, especially genetics; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Recommendations; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Derby, Miss (Box 7)
  - Derick, R. A. (Box 7)
  - DeSayda, S. D. (Box 7)
  - Detwiler, Margaret (Box 7)
  - Detwiler, S. R. (Box 7)
  - Deuber, Carl G. (Box 7)
  - Devte, Arthur H. (Box 7)
  - Deutsche Aerzte-Zeitung (Box 7)
  - Dhar, N. R. (Box 7)
  - The Dial (editor), 1904-1920; 35 items (Box 7)
    Brown, W. R.
    Doyle, Arthur Conan, Sir; Publication -- Dial; Reviews
  - Dickerson, Albert I. (Box 7)
    Laing, Alexander
  - Dickinson, Robert L. (Box 7)
    Committee on Maternal Health
    Committee on Eugenics and Dysgenics of Birth Regulation
  - Dittus, C. W. (Box 7)
  - Doggett, Marguerite V. (Box 7)
  - Dohme, Alfred R. L. (Box 7)
  - Dohrn, Anton (Box 7)
  - Donaldson, Emma (Box 7)
  - Donaldson, Henry H. (Box 7)
  - Dorfman, Joseph (Box 7)
  - Dorr, A. W. (Box 7)
  - Drake University (Box 7)
  - Driesch, Hans (Box 7)
  - Dublin, Louis I. (Box 7)
    Lusk, Graham
  - Duerden, J. E. (Box 7)
  - Dufrenoy, Jean (Box 7)
  - Dunbar, Frances (Box 7)
  - Duncker, Georg (Box 7)
  - Dunkerly, J. S. (Box 7)
  - Dunn, Gano (Box 7)
    Committee on Relation of National Research Council to National Academy of Sciences
  - Dunn, Halbert L. (Box 7)
  - Dunn, Leslie Clarence (Box 7)
  - DuPont, Pierre S. (Box 7)
  - Earle, Swepson (Box 7)
  - Earp, J. Rosslyn (Box 7)
  - East, E. M. (Edward Murray), 1911-1931; 9 folders (270 items) (Box 7)
    Conferences and symposia; Drosophila genetics; Editorial matters; Eugenics; Harvard University -- Bussey Institute; Honors; International Union for the Scientific Investigation of Population Problems; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Population, demography; Publication; Referee's report; Reviews; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; World War I -- Impact on science
    - Folder 1 (Box 7)
    - Folder 2 (Box 7)
    - Folder 3 (Box 7)
      Shull, George H.
    - Folder 4 (Box 7)
    - Folder 5 (Box 7)
    - Folder 6 (Box 7)
    - Folder 7 (Box 7)
      Morgan, Thomas Hunt
      Dunn, Gano
    - Folder 8 (Box 7)
      Bailey, Irving W.
      Day, Edmund E.
    - Folder 9 (Box 7)
  - Eckels, Richard P. (Box 7)
  - Edge, P. Granville (Box 7)
  - Edgeworth, F. B. (Box 7)
  - Edinger, Tilly (Box 7)
  - Edsall, David L. (Box 7)
  - Ehrenfest, Hugo (Box 7)
  - Eiger, Yeshivah Rabbi Akibah (Box 7)
  - Eighth American Scientific Congress, 1939-1940; 6 folders (Box 8)
    Conferences and symposia; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics
    - Folder 1 (Box 8)
      Welles, Sumner
    - Folder 2 (Box 8)
    - Folder 3 (Box 8)
      Rice, Stuart A.
      Methorst, H. W.
      Dunn, Halbert L.
    - Folder 4 (Box 8)
      Stephan, Frederick F.
      Wetmore, A.
    - Folder 5 (Box 8)
      Phelps, Elizabeth
      Cudmore, S. A.
    - Folder 6 (Box 8)
      Clark, Austin H.
      Jackson, Charles E.
      Watson, Thomas J.
  - Elliott, L. B. (Box 8)
  - Ellis, Havelock (Box 8)
  - Ellis, T. A. (Box 8)
  - Embree, Edwin R., 1924-1930; 5 folders (167 items) (Box 8)
    Drosophila genetics; Harvard University -- Pearl, Raymond; History of biology, especially genetics; Johns Hopkins University; Physiology -- Longevity; Publication; Recommendations -- LeBlanc, Thomas J.; Recommendations -- Weinstein, Alexander; Research support; Rockefeller Foundation; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
    - Folder 1 (Box 8)
      Emerson, C. F.
      Emerson, R. A.
    - Folder 2 (Box 8)
      Trowbridge, Augustus
    - Folder 3 (Box 8)
    - Folder 4 (Box 8)
      Goodnow, Frank J.
    - Folder 5 (Box 8)
  - Emerson, C. F. (Box 8)
  - Emerson, Haven (Box 8)
  - Emerson, Natt W. (Box 8)
  - Emerson, R. A. (Box 8)
  - Emslie, Raymond G. (Box 8)
  - Encyclopaedia Britannica, 1925-1927; 2 folders (Box 8)
    Publication -- Encyclopedia Britannica
  - Engelmann, Wilhelm (Box 8)
  - Enoch Pratt Library (Box 8)
    Wheeler, Joseph L.
  - Enriques, Federigo (Box 8)
  - Enriques, Paolo (Box 8)
  - Environment: Geology, Forestry (Box 8)
  - Epstein, H. (Box 8)
  - Evans, York (Box 8)
  - Ewer, Mrs. R. F. (Box 8)
  - Fairchild, David (Box 8)
  - Fairchild, H. P. (Box 8)
  - Fairchild, Milton (Box 8)
  - Farrar and Rinehart, Inc. (Box 8)
  - Fawcett, C. B. (Box 8)
  - Fayle, Jane L. (Box 8)
  - Fellman, A. M. (Box 8)
  - Fetcher, Edwin S., Jr. (Box 8)
    Geiling, E. M. K.
    Hibbits, Augusta K.
  - Field, Herbert Haviland (Box 9)
  - Fields, Harold (Box 9)
  - Fink, Harold K. (Box 9)
  - Finlay, G. F. (Box 9)
  - Fischer, Eugen (Box 9)
  - Fischer, Gustav (Box 9)
  - Fishbein, Morris (Box 9)
  - Fisher, Arne, 1925-1939; 2 folders (76 items) (Box 9)
    Business; History of biology, especially genetics; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Political issues; Publication; Reviews; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics
    - Folder 1 (Box 9)
    - Folder 2 (Box 9)
      Stephan, Frederick S.
  - Fisher, Irving (Box 9)
  - Fisher, R. A. (Box 9)
  - Fitz, Reginald (Box 9)
  - Fletcher, Marjorie Howard (Box 9)
  - Fletcher, S. W. (Box 9)
  - Flexner, Louis (Box 9)
  - Flexner, Simon (Box 9)
  - Florida Academy of Sciences (Box 9)
  - Foot, Katharine (Box 9)
  - Footeur, William (Box 9)
  - Forbes (Box 9)
  - Forok (Box 9)
  - Forum (Box 9)
    Ogden, C. K.
    Alcorn, John
    Bakeless, John
    Leach, Henry Goddard
    Morris, Sarah A.
    Bramble, Helen M.
  - Fossler, M. L. (Box 9)
  - Franckh'sche Verlagshandlung (Box 9)
  - Frank, Glenn (Box 9)
  - Frank, Grace (Box 9)
  - Freeman, Allen (Box 9)
  - Freeman, Walter (Box 9)
  - French, W. F. (Box 9)
  - Frets, G. P. (Box 9)
  - Friede-Andreeff, M. (Margaret), 1909-1928; 2 folders (49 items) (Box 9)
    Biographical and personal data; Graduate study; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Poultry genetics; Russian politics and science; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Friedenwald, Harry (Box 9)
  - Friedenwald, Jonas (Box 9)
  - Friedli, W. (Box 9)
  - Friedmans' (Box 9)
  - Frost, E. B. (Box 9)
  - Frost, W. H. (Box 9)
  - Frumkin, G. (Box 9)
  - Furwirth, C. (Box 9)
  - Gaither, General Charles D. (Box 9)
  - Galt, William (Box 9)
  - Galton Society (Box 9)
    Gregory, William K.
    Laughlin, H. H.
    Osborn, Frederick
  - Gannett, Frank (Box 9)
    Rumely, Edward A.
  - Gannon, Joseph W. (Box 9)
  - Gardner, M. W. (Box 9)
  - Garrett, Robert (Box 9)
  - Garrison, Fielding H. (Box 9)
    Willox, David
  - Garwood, R. S. (Box 9)
  - Gary, E. Stanley (Box 9)
  - Gary, Guy L. (Box 7)
  - Garza Brito, Angel De La (Box 9)
  - Gaskell, Augusta, 1928-1939; 44 items (Box 9)
    Gaskell, Grace T.
    Publication; Reviews; Solicitations for support or contribution
  - Gaskell, Edwin (Box 9)
  - Gates, R. Ruggles (Box 9)
  - Gause, G. F. (Georgii Frantsevitch), 1930-1941; 37 items (Box 9)
    Ecology; Editorial matters; Population genetics; Population, demography; Publication
  - Gay, Frederick P. (Box 9)
  - Gelder, van (Box 9)
  - George, W. C. (Box 9)
  - Gill, Robert S. (Box 9)
  - Gilles, Helen T. (Box 9)
  - Gillet, Charles B. (Box 9)
  - Gilman, Elizabeth (Box 9)
  - Gilman, John S. (Box 10)
  - Gini, Corrado, 1927-1931; 7 folders (124 items) (Box 10)
    Biographical and personal data; Committee activities -- Population, demography; International Union for the Scientific Investigation of Population Problems; Publication; Research support; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
    - Folder 1 (Box 10)
    - Folder 2 (Box 10)
    - Folder 3 (Box 10)
      Revelli, Paolo
    - Folder 4 (Box 10)
    - Folder 5 (Box 10)
      Wilson, Edwin B.
    - Folder 6 (Box 10)
    - Folder 7 (Box 10)
  - Ginn and Company (Box 10)
  - Glenn, John M. (Box 10)
  - Godlowski, Emil (Box 10)
  - Gontcharoff, B. de (Box 10)
  - Gonzales, B. M. (Box 10)
  - Goodman, Jules Eckert (Box 10)
  - Goodman, Philip (Box 10)
  - Goodnow, Frank J. (Box 10)
    Vincent, George E.
  - Goodrich, Nathaniel L. (Box 10)
    Dartmouth College Library
  - Goodwin, L. E. (Box 10)
  - Gorbman, Aubrey (Box 10)
    Henger, R. W.
  - Gosset, W. L. (Box 10)
  - Goto, Seitano (Box 10)
  - Gotto, Mrs. S. (Box 10)
  - Gowen, John W., 1930-1940; 2 folders (67 items) (Box 10)
    Biographical and personal data; Genetics -- Cattle; Genetics -- Disease resistance; Graduate study; Mouse genetics; Poultry genetics; Publication; Rockefeller Foundation; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Graham, A. Michael (Box 10)
  - Graham, W. R. (Box 10)
  - Grant, John B. (Box 10)
  - Grape, A. H., and Company, 1927, 1930 (Box 10)
  - Graves, William Washington (Box 10)
  - Gregg, Clifford C. (Box 10)
  - Greenwood, Major, 1921-1944; 19 folders (506 items) (Box 10-11)
    Biographical and personal data; Biographical and personal data -- Dublin, Louis I.; Biographical and personal data -- Fisher, Ronald Aylmer; Biographical and personal data -- Pearson, Karl; Biographical and personal data -- Wilson, Edwin Bidwell; Business; Educational matters; Galton Laboratory; Genetics; Honors; International Congress of Eugenics -- Second Congress; Philosophy of science; Poetry and literature; Political issues; Publication; Recommendations; Reviews; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Scientific refugees; Solicitations for support or contribution; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Teaching -- Johns Hopkins University; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; World War II -- Impact on science
    - Folder 1 (Box 10)
    - Folder 2 (Box 10)
      Henderson, H. D.
    - Folder 3 (Box 10)
      Mencken, H. L.
    - Folder 4 (Box 10)
    - Folder 5 (Box 10)
    - Folder 6 (Box 10)
    - Folder 7 (Box 10)
      Vivian, S.
      Thomson, A. Landsborough
    - Folder 8 (Box 10)
      Stamp, Sir Josiah
    - Folder 9 (Box 10)
    - Folder 10 (Box 11)
    - Folder 11 (Box 11)
    - Folder 12 (Box 11)
      Greenwood, A. Lawrence
    - Folder 13 (Box 11)
    - Folder 14 (Box 11)
    - Folder 15 (Box 11)
    - Folder 16 (Box 11)
    - Folder 17 (Box 11)
    - Folder 18 (Box 11)
      Dean, H. R.
    - Folder 19 (Box 11)
  - Greenwood, Rosa (Box 11)
  - Greif, Amy F. (Box 11)
  - Griffith, Melvin E. (Box 11)
  - Gruenberg, Benjamin C. (Box 11)
  - Gruenwald, Peter (Box 11)
  - Guan, Arthur (Box 11)
  - Gudger, E. W. (Box 11)
  - Gulick, Addison (Box 11)
  - Gumbel, E. J. (Box 11)
  - Hadley, Philip B. (Box 11)
  - Hake, John L. (Box 11)
  - Hahn, Martin (Box 11)
  - Hale, George E. (Box 11)
  - Hall, Alton L. (Box 11)
  - Hall, Arnold B. (Box 11)
  - Hall, Edwin H. (Box 11)
  - Hall, G. Stanley (Box 11)
  - Hall, Milton W. (Box 11)
  - Hall, R. P. (Box 11)
  - Hamburger, Louis P. (Box 11)
  - Hamman, Louis (Box 11)
  - Hammett, Frederick S. (Box 11)
  - Hammend, E. Cuyler (Box 11)
  - Hanrahan, Edward M. Jr. (Box 11)
  - Hanson, J. M. (Box 11)
  - Harding, T. Swann (Box 11)
  - Hargrove, W. H. (Box 11)
  - Harmon, G. E. (Box 11)
  - Harper, Fowler V. (Box 11)
  - Harper Brothers (Box 11)
    Harper's Magazine
  - Harris, F. K. (Box 11)
  - Harris, J. Arthur (Box 11)
  - Harrison, Ross Granville, 1916-1941; 5 folders (133 items) (Box 11)
    Biographical and personal data; Business; Editorial matters; National Academy of Sciences; Publication -- Journal of Experimental Zoology; Recommendations; Referee's report; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; World War I -- Impact on science
    - Folder 1 (Box 11)
    - Folder 2 (Box 11)
    - Folder 3 (Box 11)
    - Folder 4 (Box 11)
    - Folder 5 (Box 11)
      Hegner, R. W.
  - Hartman, Howard R. (Box 11)
  - Harvard University (Box 11)
  - Harvey, H. E. (Box 11)
    Rhein, M. L.
    Gillett, H. W.
  - Haskell, A. C. (Box 12)
  - Hastings, Harold R. (Box 12)
  - Hatai, Shinkishi (Box 12)
  - Hatcher, J. B. (Box 12)
  - Hawkes, Ralph W. (Box 12)
  - Hawkes, Mrs. O. A. Merritt (Box 12)
  - Hawley, Paul R. (Box 12)
  - Hayner, Leonidos (Box 12)
  - Hayward, Sidney C. (Box 12)
    Greenwood, Major
  - Headland, Mrs. Isaac Taylor (Box 12)
  - Heath, D. C. (Box 12)
  - Hegner, R. W. (Box 12)
  - Hektoen, Ludwig (Box 12)
  - Hemburger, Theodore (Box 12)
  - Henderson, Edith T. (Box 12)
  - Henderson, Lawrence J., 1914-1940; 8 folders (279 items) (Box 12)
    Lowes, John Livingston
    Biographical and personal data; Business; Cancer, chemotherapy; Editorial matters; Harvard University; History of biology, especially genetics; Johns Hopkins University; Physiology; Physiology -- Longevity; Publication; Research support; Reviews; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Teaching; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Henry, Daniel M. (Box 12)
  - Henry, Frank F. (Box 12)
  - Hergesheimer, Joseph (Box 12)
  - Hermannsson, H. (Box 12)
  - Hernando, Eugenio (Box 12)
  - Heron, David (Box 12)
  - Herrera, A. L. (Box 12)
  - Herskovits, Melville J. (Box 12)
  - Hertwig, R. (Box 12)
  - Herwerden, M. A. van (Box 12)
  - Hesketh, Florence E. (Box 12)
  - Hill, A. Bradford (Box 12)
  - Hill, Arthur (Box 12)
  - Hiller, Paul W. (Box 12)
  - Hinrichs, Ernest H. (Box 12)
  - History of Science Society (Box 12)
    Browne, Charles A.
    Brasch, Frederick E.
  - Hoban, Owen A. (Box 12)